gleanster.com 2011-12-25

# Gleanster - Terms of Use and Privacy Policy

## (Legal Mumbo Jumbo: Not Brief, Very Specific, Quite Objective)

PLEASE REVIEW THE FOLLOWING INFORMATION CAREFULLY. USE OF GLEANSTER.COM AND THE MATERIALS HEREIN WILL INDICATE YOUR AGREEMENT TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS BELOW. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS, PLEASE EXIT THIS SITE.

#### Information Collection and Use

When you register on the Gleanster website, download a Gleansight benchmark report or purchase Gleanster products or services, we ask you for personal information. We use this information to provide you with high quality service and with recommendations that we think may be useful to you. We may also contact you regarding a website problem or other customer service-related issues. Note: Gleanster does not market to children and does not knowingly collect personal information from children.

#### Usage Tracking

We may monitor how you use the Gleanster website including search terms you enter, pages visited and documents viewed. If you are a registered user, this information is stored with your registration information. It is used solely to allow us to provide you with a personalized Web site experience. Aggregated (not personally identifiable) forms of this data may also be used in order to help us understand areas for future research and to identify features that can improve the website experience. This data may also be used by Gleanster, in the aggregate, to identify appropriate product offerings and subscription plans.

#### Cookies

A cookie is a small piece of computer code that enables Web servers to "identify" visitors. Each time you initiate a session on Gleanster, a cookie is set in order to identify you and determine your access privileges. Cookies do not store any of the information that you have provided to the site. They are simply identifiers. You have the ability to delete cookie files from your hard drive at any time. However, you should know that cookies may be necessary to provide you with access to certain features of the Gleanster website. We use cookie technology to enable registered users to move quickly and securely through access-controlled areas of the site.

#### Information Sharing and Disclosure

Gleanster reserves the right to share information submitted by individuals who have opted to download a Gleansight benchmark report for free with up to three (3) technology solution providers whose go-to-market messages are aligned with the topic of that particular report. These technology solution providers may contact you to provide additional guidance as you seek to implement a related technology-enabled business initiative and to explore opportunities for working together.

#### How to Unsubscribe

If you no longer wish to receive e-mail communications from Gleanster, you may unsubscribe by clicking the "Unsubscribe" button at the bottom of each e-mail Gleanster sends. You may also opt-in or opt-out of Gleanster communication from your profile on Gleanster.com.

#### Registration

In order to use many features on the Gleanster website, you may be asked to complete a registration form. During registration, you are required to provide contact information which is used to determine whether you are a subscriber.

  * Gleanster LLC reserves the right to take any of the following actions at any time and for any reason without giving you any prior notice:
  * Restrict, suspend, or terminate access to all or any part of Gleanster.com
  * Change, suspend, or discontinue all or any part of Gleanster.com
  * Refuse, move, or remove any material that you submit to Gleanster.com for any reason
  * Refuse, move, or remove any content that is available on Gleanster.com
  * Institute general standards and limits concerning Gleanster.com.

You agree that Gleanster LLC will not be liable to you or any third party for taking any of these actions.

#### Purchases and Fulfillment

When you place an order or register for a Gleanster event, we may request additional information such as credit card number and expiration date. This information is used for billing purposes. The contact information you provide is used to service the order. Also, when you register for an event, we may request additional information about your accommodations or travel schedule. This information is used only for the relevant event. Gleanster uses third-party service providers such as credit card processing companies, mailing houses and event coordinators along with other service providers to satisfy client requests.

#### Usage Entitlements

Username and Passwords are for individual use, they may not be shared with others.

#### Content Usage

If you would like to request permission to use any of the content on the Site, please request permission via email to [ ](mailto:%20%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20var%20prefix%20=%20'mailto:';%20var%20suffix%20=%20'';%20var%20attribs%20=%20'';%20var%20path%20=%20'hr'%20+%20'ef'%20+%20'=';%20var%20addy96335%20=%20'support'%20+%20'@';%20addy96335%20=%20addy96335%20+%20'gleanster'%20+%20'.'%20+%20'com';%20document.write\(%20'%3Ca%20'%20+%20path%20+%20'\\''%20+%20prefix%20+%20addy96335%20+%20suffix%20+%20'\\''%20+%20attribs%20+%20'%3E'%20\);%20document.write\(%20addy96335%20\);%20document.write\(%20'%3C\\/a%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\(%20'%3Cspan%20style=\\'display:%20none;\\'%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3EThis%20e-mail%20address%20is%20being%20protected%20from%20spambots.%20You%20need%20JavaScript%20enabled%20to%20view%20it%20%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\(%20'%3C/'%20\);%20document.write\(%20'span%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E.)[support@gleanster.com](mailto:support@gleanster.com).

The Site contains content that we create as well as content provided by third parties. This content includes, among other things, product reviews, case studies, research reports, and user quotes. It also includes information about products and services offered by parties other than Gleanster, such as product descriptions, press releases, specifications, pricing, availability, and performance. We do not guarantee the accuracy, the integrity, or the quality of the content on the Site, and you may not rely on any of this content. Without limitation, we are not responsible for postings by users in the user opinion, message board, or feedback sections of the Site.

#### Links to Other Sites

Gleansight benchmark reports and other Gleanster documents may contain links to other websites. Gleanster is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. As such, this privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Gleanster.

#### Security

Gleanster tries to provides users with a secure online experience. All user registration information is contained behind a firewall and only accessible by a limited number of employees who have special access rights to our operational systems. To do this, we use a variety of security measures to maintain the safety and confidentiality of personal information about you.

#### Updating Personal Information

If your personal information changes, you may update it at any time on Gleanster.com . To correct or update personal information, go to your user profile on the Gleanster website. We encourage you to do this on a regular basis to keep abreast of new research, emerging trends, and best practices.

#### Notification of Policy Changes

You will be notified of changes to our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy through links on our website and in some instances, we may send a notice to the primary e-mail address specified in your user profile.

#### Indemnification

You agree to indemnify, defend and hold Gleanster LLC and all of its officers, directors, owners, employees, agents, information providers, affiliates, partners, and licensors (collectively, the "Gleanster LLC Parties") harmless from and against any and all liability, losses, costs, and expenses (including attorneys' fees) incurred by any Gleanster LLC Party in connection with any claim, including, but not limited to, claims for defamation, violation of rights of publicity and/or privacy, copyright infringement, or trademark infringement arising out of:

Gleanster LLC reserves the right, at our own expense, to defend any matter for which you are required to indemnify us, and you agree to cooperate with our defense of these claims.

If you believe that content you own has been copied and made accessible in a manner that violates your intellectual property rights, please contact [ ](mailto:%20%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20var%20prefix%20=%20'mailto:';%20var%20suffix%20=%20'';%20var%20attribs%20=%20'';%20var%20path%20=%20'hr'%20+%20'ef'%20+%20'=';%20var%20addy74977%20=%20'support'%20+%20'@';%20addy74977%20=%20addy74977%20+%20'gleanster'%20+%20'.'%20+%20'com';%20document.write\(%20'%3Ca%20'%20+%20path%20+%20'\\''%20+%20prefix%20+%20addy74977%20+%20suffix%20+%20'\\''%20+%20attribs%20+%20'%3E'%20\);%20document.write\(%20addy74977%20\);%20document.write\(%20'%3C\\/a%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\(%20'%3Cspan%20style=\\'display:%20none;\\'%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3EThis%20e-mail%20address%20is%20being%20protected%20from%20spambots.%20You%20need%20JavaScript%20enabled%20to%20view%20it%20%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\(%20'%3C/'%20\);%20document.write\(%20'span%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E.)[support@gleanster.com](mailto:support@gleanster.com).

#### **Guidelines for Third Party Content Submitted to (and Made Accessible From) the Open Resource Library**

The Open Resource Library section of the Gleanster website aggregates and provides access to content such as white papers, research reports, case studies and presentations submitted by third parties, including market search firms, consultancies, and technology solution providers. While Gleanster screens all content submissions for quality and relevance, and also seeks to verify that the party submitting the content is the true copyright holder, Gleanster ultimately assumes no responsibility for any content submitted by a third party. 

Parties submitting content should understand that, whether or not their content is approved and made available in the Open Resource Library, Gleanster does not guarantee any confidentiality or security. In addition, by submitting content, parties affirm, represent, and/or warrant that they own or have the necessary licenses, rights, consents, and permissions and authorize Gleanster to use all trademark, copyright or other proprietary rights so as to enable inclusion of the content in the Open Resource Library and access to the content by Gleanster users.

By submitting content to the Open Resource Library, you hereby grant Gleanster a worldwide, non-exclusive, royalty-free license to use, distribute, promote and display the content in connection with Gleanster’s business, including without limitation the ability to promote and redistribute part or all of the content through other distribution channels, such as email. You also hereby grant each user of the Gleanster website a non-exclusive license to access your content.

Gleanster does not permit copyright infringing activities and infringement of intellectual property rights and will promptly remove all content if properly notified that such content infringes on another's intellectual property rights. Gleanster responds to notices of alleged copyright infringement that comply with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act. If you believe that content you own has been submitted to the Open Resource Library without your or your company's authorization, please contact [ ](mailto:%20%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20var%20prefix%20=%20'mailto:';%20var%20suffix%20=%20'';%20var%20attribs%20=%20'';%20var%20path%20=%20'hr'%20+%20'ef'%20+%20'=';%20var%20addy82839%20=%20'support'%20+%20'@';%20addy82839%20=%20addy82839%20+%20'gleanster'%20+%20'.'%20+%20'com';%20document.write\(%20'%3Ca%20'%20+%20path%20+%20'\\''%20+%20prefix%20+%20addy82839%20+%20suffix%20+%20'\\''%20+%20attribs%20+%20'%3E'%20\);%20document.write\(%20addy82839%20\);%20document.write\(%20'%3C\\/a%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\(%20'%3Cspan%20style=\\'display:%20none;\\'%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3EThis%20e-mail%20address%20is%20being%20protected%20from%20spambots.%20You%20need%20JavaScript%20enabled%20to%20view%20it%20%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\(%20'%3C/'%20\);%20document.write\(%20'span%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E.)[support@gleanster.com](mailto:support@gleanster.com). Gleanster reserves the right to remove third-party content without prior notice.

As a user of the Open Resource Library, you agree that Gleanster is not responsible for the accuracy, usefulness, or intellectual property rights of or relating to content included in the Open Resource Library. Gleanster does not warrant, endorse, guarantee, or assume responsibility for any third-party content and, furthermore, disclaims any responsibility for the deletion or unauthorized distribution of any content submitted to the Open Resource Library.
